[
  {
    "_id": "641f7ea723a50619ba9b45ea",
    "survey": "641f6e6323a50619ba9b459f",
    "answers": [
      {
        "question": "641f6e6323a50619ba9b459a",
        "answer": 4,
        "_id": "641f7ea723a50619ba9b45eb"
      },
      {
        "question": "641f6e6323a50619ba9b459b",
        "answer": "Yes",
        "_id": "641f7ea723a50619ba9b45ec"
      },
      {
        "question": "641f6e6323a50619ba9b459c",
        "answer": "I enjoy the flexibility of my work schedule.",
        "_id": "641f7ea723a50619ba9b45ed"
      },
      {
        "question": "641f6e6323a50619ba9b459d",
        "answer": "I don't like it when information is not communicated as it should be",
        "_id": "641f7ea723a50619ba9b45ee"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "_id": "641f835688c613343ee9b5d8",
    "survey": "641f6e6323a50619ba9b459f",
    "answers": [
      {
        "question": "641f6e6323a50619ba9b459a",
        "answer": 3,
        "_id": "641f835688c613343ee9b5d9"
      },
      {
        "question": "641f6e6323a50619ba9b459b",
        "answer": "No",
        "_id": "641f835688c613343ee9b5da"
      },
      {
        "question": "641f6e6323a50619ba9b459c",
        "answer": "Bla bla blah.",
        "_id": "641f835688c613343ee9b5db"
      },
      {
        "question": "641f6e6323a50619ba9b459d",
        "answer": "Bla bla blah.",
        "_id": "641f835688c613343ee9b5dc"
      }
    ],
    "meta": {
      "ipAddress": "192.168.1.101",
      "userAgent": "Mozilla/5.0 (Macintosh; Intel Mac OS X 10_15_7) AppleWebKit/537.36 (KHTML, like Gecko) Chrome/97.0.4692.99 Safari/537.36"
    },
    "__v": 0
  },
  {
    "_id": "641f83cf88c613343ee9b5e0",
    "survey": "641f6e6323a50619ba9b459f",
    "answers": [
      {
        "question": "641f6e6323a50619ba9b459a",
        "answer": 5,
        "_id": "641f83cf88c613343ee9b5e1"
      },
      {
        "question": "641f6e6323a50619ba9b459b",
        "answer": "Yes",
        "_id": "641f83cf88c613343ee9b5e2"
      },
      {
        "question": "641f6e6323a50619ba9b459c",
        "answer": "I enjoy the collaborative environment and working with my team.",
        "_id": "641f83cf88c613343ee9b5e3"
      },
      {
        "question": "641f6e6323a50619ba9b459d",
        "answer": "I do not like the long commute to work.",
        "_id": "641f83cf88c613343ee9b5e4"
      }
    ],
    "meta": {
      "location": "New York, USA",
      "ipAddress": "192.168.0.1",
      "userAgent": "Mozilla/5.0 (Macintosh; Intel Mac OS X 10_15_7) AppleWebKit/537.36 (KHTML, like Gecko) Chrome/97.0.4692.99 Safari/537.36"
    }
  },
  {
    "_id": "641f856d88c613343ee9b5e8",
    "survey": "641f7ad723a50619ba9b45c0",
    "answers": [
      {
        "question": "641f7ad723a50619ba9b45bb",
        "answer": 5,
        "_id": "641f856d88c613343ee9b5e9"
      },
      {
        "question": "641f7ad723a50619ba9b45bc",
        "answer": ["Product A", "Product B"],
        "_id": "641f856d88c613343ee9b5ea"
      },
      {
        "question": "641f7ad723a50619ba9b45bd",
        "answer": "Good",
        "_id": "641f856d88c613343ee9b5eb"
      },
      {
        "question": "641f7ad723a50619ba9b45be",
        "answer": "I think you could improve your delivery times.",
        "_id": "641f856d88c613343ee9b5ec"
      }
    ],
    "meta": {
      "location": "New York, USA",
      "ipAddress": "192.168.0.1",
      "userAgent": "Mozilla/5.0 (Macintosh; Intel Mac OS X 10_15_7) AppleWebKit/537.36 (KHTML, like Gecko) Chrome/97.0.4692.99 Safari/537.36"
    }
  },
  {
    "_id": "641f85a488c613343ee9b5f0",
    "survey": "641f7ad723a50619ba9b45c0",
    "answers": [
      {
        "question": "641f7ad723a50619ba9b45bb",
        "answer": 4,
        "_id": "641f85a488c613343ee9b5f1"
      },
      {
        "question": "641f7ad723a50619ba9b45bc",
        "answer": ["Product A", "Product C"],
        "_id": "641f85a488c613343ee9b5f2"
      },
      {
        "question": "641f7ad723a50619ba9b45bd",
        "answer": "Fair",
        "_id": "641f85a488c613343ee9b5f3"
      },
      {
        "question": "641f7ad723a50619ba9b45be",
        "answer": "Bla blah blah...",
        "_id": "641f85a488c613343ee9b5f4"
      }
    ],
    "meta": {
      "location": "New York, USA",
      "ipAddress": "192.168.0.1",
      "userAgent": "Mozilla/5.0 (Macintosh; Intel Mac OS X 10_15_7) AppleWebKit/537.36 (KHTML, like Gecko) Chrome/97.0.4692.99 Safari/537.36"
    }
  },
  {
    "_id": "641f85b788c613343ee9b5f8",
    "survey": "641f7ad723a50619ba9b45c0",
    "answers": [
      {
        "question": "641f7ad723a50619ba9b45bb",
        "answer": 3,
        "_id": "641f85b788c613343ee9b5f9"
      },
      {
        "question": "641f7ad723a50619ba9b45bc",
        "answer": ["Product B", "Product C"],
        "_id": "641f85b788c613343ee9b5fa"
      },
      {
        "question": "641f7ad723a50619ba9b45bd",
        "answer": "Poor",
        "_id": "641f85b788c613343ee9b5fb"
      },
      {
        "question": "641f7ad723a50619ba9b45be",
        "answer": "Bla blah blah...",
        "_id": "641f85b788c613343ee9b5fc"
      }
    ],
    "meta": {
      "location": "New York, USA",
      "ipAddress": "192.168.0.1",
      "userAgent": "Mozilla/5.0 (Macintosh; Intel Mac OS X 10_15_7) AppleWebKit/537.36 (KHTML, like Gecko) Chrome/97.0.4692.99 Safari/537.36"
    }
  },
  {
    "_id": "641f868288c613343ee9b600",
    "survey": "641f7aea23a50619ba9b45c7",
    "answers": [
      {
        "question": "641f7aea23a50619ba9b45c3",
        "answer": "Daily",
        "_id": "641f868288c613343ee9b601"
      },
      {
        "question": "641f7aea23a50619ba9b45c4",
        "answer": ["Price", "Quality", "Brand"],
        "_id": "641f868288c613343ee9b602"
      },
      {
        "question": "641f7aea23a50619ba9b45c5",
        "answer": 120,
        "_id": "641f868288c613343ee9b603"
      }
    ],
    "meta": {
      "ipAddress": "192.168.0.1",
      "userAgent": "Mozilla/5.0 (Macintosh; Intel Mac OS X 10_15_7) AppleWebKit/537.36 (KHTML, like Gecko) Chrome/97.0.4692.99 Safari/537.36"
    }
  },
  {
    "_id": "641f8a5888c613343ee9b635",
    "survey": "641f7aea23a50619ba9b45c7",
    "answers": [
      {
        "question": "641f7aea23a50619ba9b45c3",
        "answer": "Daily",
        "_id": "641f8a5888c613343ee9b636"
      },
      {
        "question": "641f7aea23a50619ba9b45c4",
        "answer": ["Price", "Brand"],
        "_id": "641f8a5888c613343ee9b637"
      },
      {
        "question": "641f7aea23a50619ba9b45c5",
        "answer": 80,
        "_id": "641f8a5888c613343ee9b638"
      }
    ],
    "meta": {
      "ipAddress": "192.168.0.1",
      "userAgent": "Mozilla/5.0 (Macintosh; Intel Mac OS X 10_15_7) AppleWebKit/537.36 (KHTML, like Gecko) Chrome/97.0.4692.99 Safari/537.36"
    }
  },
  {
    "_id": "641f8a6088c613343ee9b63c",
    "survey": "641f7aea23a50619ba9b45c7",
    "answers": [
      {
        "question": "641f7aea23a50619ba9b45c3",
        "answer": "Weekly",
        "_id": "641f8a6088c613343ee9b63d"
      },
      {
        "question": "641f7aea23a50619ba9b45c4",
        "answer": ["Price", "Brand"],
        "_id": "641f8a6088c613343ee9b63e"
      },
      {
        "question": "641f7aea23a50619ba9b45c5",
        "answer": 90,
        "_id": "641f8a6088c613343ee9b63f"
      }
    ],
    "meta": {
      "ipAddress": "192.168.0.1",
      "userAgent": "Mozilla/5.0 (Macintosh; Intel Mac OS X 10_15_7) AppleWebKit/537.36 (KHTML, like Gecko) Chrome/97.0.4692.99 Safari/537.36"
    }
  },
  {
    "_id": "641f8a6a88c613343ee9b643",
    "survey": "641f7aea23a50619ba9b45c7",
    "answers": [
      {
        "question": "641f7aea23a50619ba9b45c3",
        "answer": "Monthly",
        "_id": "641f8a6a88c613343ee9b644"
      },
      {
        "question": "641f7aea23a50619ba9b45c4",
        "answer": ["Price", "Brand"],
        "_id": "641f8a6a88c613343ee9b645"
      },
      {
        "question": "641f7aea23a50619ba9b45c5",
        "answer": 100,
        "_id": "641f8a6a88c613343ee9b646"
      }
    ],
    "meta": {
      "ipAddress": "192.168.0.1",
      "userAgent": "Mozilla/5.0 (Macintosh; Intel Mac OS X 10_15_7) AppleWebKit/537.36 (KHTML, like Gecko) Chrome/97.0.4692.99 Safari/537.36"
    }
  }
]
